We're just standing behind her.
(Sheldon:)It's not like we're gonna say
"boo" and scare her.
(Penny:)How could you not tell us
you were in beauty pageants?
'Cause it's
embarrassing.
(laughing):
It is; it truly is.
(Bernadette:)Yeah, well...
Amy writes Little House
on the Prairie fan fiction
(Bernadette:)about herself
and posts it on the Internet.
No!
Why? What did I do?!
(Bernadette:)Sorry, I had to get
the spotlight off me,
(Bernadette:)and tearing down other women
is part of my pageant training.
(Penny:)Okay. We are
reading that right now.
(Amy:)No, please don't.
(Bernadette:)We got embarrassed
tonight. Come on.
(Amy:)But it's personal.
(Penny:)Why? Is it about you
and Sheldon?
(chuckles):
No.
(Penny:)Oh, my God, it's
about her and Sheldon.
(Amy:)It's not about me and Sheldon.
(Amy:)It's about a young woman
in the 1800s named Amelia...
(Amy:)and the time-traveling physicist
named Cooper
(Amy:)she falls in love with.